<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quotes"><item>You are the best!</item>
        <item>Good, better, best. Never let it rest. \'Til your good is better and your better is best. \n(St. Jerome)</item>
        <item>Either you run the day or the day runs you. \n(John Rohn)</item>
        <item>Accept the challenges so that you can feel the exhilaration of victory. \n(George S. Patton)</item>
        <item>In order to succeed, we must first believe that we can. \n(Nikos Kazantzakis</item>
        <item>When you reach the end of your rope, tie a knot in it and hang on. \n(Franklin D. Roosevelt)</item>
        <item>Life is 10% what happens to you and 90% how you react to it. \n(Charles R. Swindoll)</item>
        <item>Failure will never overtake me if my determination to succeed is strong enough. \n(Og Mandino)</item>
        <item>What you do today can improve all your tomorrows. \n(Ralph Martson)</item>
        <item>A creative man is motivated by the desire to achieve, not by the desire to beat others. \n(Ayn Rand)</item>
        <item>The secret of getting ahead is getting started. \n(Mark Twain)</item>
        <item>The best preparation for tomorrow is doing your best today. \n(H. Jackson Brown, Jr)</item>
        <item>The best and most beautiful things in the world cannot be seen or even touched - they must be felt with the heart. \n (Helen Keller(</item>
        <item>I can\'t change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination. \n(Jimmy Dean)</item>
        <item>Start by doing what\'s necessary; then do what\'s possible; and suddenly you are doing the impossible. \n(Francis of Assisi)</item>
        <item>Perfection is not attainable, but if we chase perfection we can catch excellence. \n(Vince Lombardi)</item>
        <item>We must let go of the life we have planned, so as to accept the one that is waiting for us. \n(Joseph Campbell)</item>
        <item>Nothing is impossible, the word itself says "I\'m possible"! \n(Audrey Hepburn)</item>
        <item>Try to be a rainbow in someone\'s cloud. \n(Maya Angelou)</item>
        <item>We know what we are, but know not what we may be. \n(William Shakespeare)</item>
        <item>Change your thoughts and you change your world. \n(Norman Vincent Peale)</item>
        <item>If you can\'t stop thinking about it, don\'t stop working on it.</item>
        <item>A river cuts through rock not because of its power, but its persistence.</item>
        <item>Don\'t be afraid to start over. It\'s a brand new opportunity to rebuild what you truly want.</item>
        <item>The best way to predict the future is to create it.</item>
        <item>In order to succeed we must first believe that we can. \n(Nikos Kazantzakis)</item>
        <item>Do it now! \nSometimes "later" becomes "never".</item>
        <item>You have to fight through the bad days to earn the best days.</item>
        <item>Nothing worth having comes easy.</item>
        <item>Do something today that your future self will thank you for.</item>
        <item>A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new. \n(Albert Einstein)</item>
        <item>Sometimes you win, sometimes you learn.</item>
        <item>Work until your idols become your rivals. \n(Drake)</item>
        <item>You got this!</item>
        <item>What you do today can improve all your tomorrows.</item>
        <item>If "Plan A" didn\'t work, the alphabet has 25 more letters.</item>
        <item>To hell with circumstances. I create opportunities! \n(Bruce Lee)</item>
        <item>Mistakes are proof that you are trying.</item>
        <item>Believe in the person you want to become.</item>
        <item>Don\'t worry about those who talks about you behind your back. They are behind for a reason.</item>
        <item>Don\'t count the days. Make the days count.</item>
        <item>When you feel like quitting, think about why you started.</item>
        <item>Your only limit is you!</item>
        <item>Your future is created by what you do today. Not tomorrow.</item>
        <item>It\'s hard to beat a person who never gives up. \n(Babe Ruth)</item>
        <item>Prove them wrong!</item>
        <item>Whether you think you can, or you think you can\'t, you are right. \n(Henry Ford)</item>
        <item>When you want to succeed as bad as you want to breathe, then you\'ll be successful.</item>
        <item>Just do it!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>